redrocksonline.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Red Rocks Entertainment Concerts

The City and County of Denver is committed to protecting user privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the Web will not only protect users, but also increase user confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. At www.redrocksonline.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather when you visit our sites, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. The following is the privacy policy for this site (all pages starting with www.redrocksonline.com).

If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that emails us this information, we will only use the personally identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question.

We collect some information that is used for analysis and statistical purposes that help us manage the RedRocksonline site.

1) Information that we collect for statistical purposes  
We automatically collect electronically generated information about your visit to our site, such as the date, type of browser used, and technical Internet protocol data. We collect this information about each user session from our user logs, and refer to it for statistical purposes.

2) Information that you provide us when using our interactive forms and functions. This information may include such things as name, address, telephone number, and other personal and business data.

3) Opting-out  
At any time while assessing our site(s), any user while online may "opt-out" of further email contact from us (while still allowing access to our sites).

4) Control of personal information  
At any time, while assessing our site(s), any user while online may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e. survey or email). Your choice not to participate will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature on our site(s). In online applications that ask for personal information, you also are provided the option of canceling or "clearing all fields" of information and terminating the application. You also may request that email messages you send to the City of Denver be deleted from email archives once the communication or transaction is completed. You also are provided an automatic way to "unsubscribe" to any newsletters, notices, schedules, etc., sent to you automatically by email.

5) Use of cookies  
We do not use "persistent" cookies to collect permanent information. (Note: A cookie file contains unique information a Web site can use to track such things as passwords, lists of pages you've visited, and the date when you last looked at a specific page, or to identify your session at a particular Web site. A cookie is often used in commercial sites to identify the items selected for a specific shopping cart application.)

We do use "non-persistent" cookies in applications that keep track of a user and make it possible for you to complete a form or use a function.

6) Disclosure to third parties  
As a governmental agency, we are governed by open records laws. Any information that we receive through use of our site is subject to the same provisions as information provided on paper. Otherwise, we do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties. Our privacy policy will apply to these websites, and we require those organizations to adhere to our privacy policy, and will not share personal information with any third party without your permission.

This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties unless we are legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings.

Visit the [Denvergov.org privacy policy](https://www.denvergov.org/content/denvergov/en/city-of-denver-home/privacy-policy.html).
